lightdials.com 2018-01-02

# 

Privacy

THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT EXPLAINS MAGIC AURORA TECH LTD’s INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE POLICIES, WITH RESPECT TO THE WEBSITES, SERVICES, PRODUCTS AND TECHNOLOGY.

Information Gathering and Usage

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our service, the Application and features and content relating thereto (together, the Service) and to enable users to enjoy the Service. Information we collect may include:

When installing for Light Dial we collect anonymous usage data using an industry standard third party analytic service (such as Google Analytic) to better understand the performance of our service. The information we collect via third party services does not contain personal information. The information we collect is used to improve Light Dial and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to others.

If you use our search service, we may collect your search terms. The search feature, in the course of processing a given search query, will send a request to our servers. This request includes the keyword query, time of day, browser type, default language setting, and IP address, an anonymous unique ID. We use this information to properly process your search request. Such information is recorded on a non-personally identifiable basis, is kept strictly anonymous and is Non-Identifying Information. In addition, all information about search activity is evaluated only on an aggregated basis (except in response to a customer service inquiry or legal process).

Your Data

Light Dial uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run it. Although Light Dial owns the code, databases, and all rights to the application, you retain all rights to your data.

Disclosure

We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

Compliance

Light Dial cooperates with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information we have to government or law enforcement officials while it is necessary to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Light Dial, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

Change

We may, from time to time, change this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to visit and review this Policy frequently to stay informed. Prior to any material change to this Privacy Policy, Light Dial will present some detailed notification.

Contact

Any concerns, you may contact us at:

Address: UNIT8, 21/F KF COMM BLDG, 87 ARGYLE ST MONGKOK KLN HONG KONG
